https://www.ahslawyers.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.ahslawyers.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING
Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP will use your information to respond to you, regarding your legal issue or other reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION
You may opt out of any future contacts from Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SECURITY
Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
LINKS
The pages on this website, including our Resources and Blog pages contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
If you feel that Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP is not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (818) 501-5800 or via the contact form on our website.
Business Disputes
Business Organization
Business Succession Planning
Sales and Acquisitions
Trademarks and Copyrights
Intellectual Property and Litigation
Probate and Estate Litigation
Leasing
www.ahslawyers.com
WOODLAND HILLS OFFICE: 21700 W Oxnard St #1160 • Woodland Hills, CA 91367
• P: (818) 501-5800 • F: (818) 869-1512
LOS ANGELES OFFICE: P: (310) 519-0324 • F: (818) 869-1512
Home | Firm Overview | Attorney Profiles | Practice Areas Overview | Resources | Contact Us
Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP has offices in Woodland Hills, California, and Valencia (Santa Clarita), California. We represent clients from Sherman Oaks, Encino, Calabasas, Thousand Oaks, Westlake Village, Ventura, Oxnard, Valencia, and throughout Southern California in such counties as Los Angeles County, Orange County, and Ventura County.
© 2020 by Hymes, Schreiber & Walden, LLP. All rights reserved. Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | Site Map
Search Engine Optimization by Web Reputation Builders.
